kill this guy
saying.
#F
#This guy just saying.
Is that what you want?
#F
#Is that what you want?
Here's a little holiday
greeting. I've been wanting
to send to the Mandarin. I
just didn't know how to
phrase it until now.
#F
#Here's a little holiday greeting. I've been wanting to send to the Mandarin. I just didn't know how to phrase it until now.
My name is Tony Stark and I'm
not afraid of you. I know
you're a coward. So I've
decided that you just died
pal. I'm gonna come get the
body. There's no politics
here. It's just good
old-fashioned Revenge. It's
no Pentagon. It's just you
and me on the off chance
Superman. Here's my home
address 10
880 Malibu
.90 265
#F
#My name is Tony Stark and I'm not afraid of you. I know you're a coward. So I've decided that you just died pal. I'm going to come get the body. There's no politics here. It's just good old-fashioned Revenge. It's no Pentagon. It's just you and me on the off chance Superman. Here's my home address 10. 880 Malibu .90 265
I'll leave the door unlocked.
That's what you want to drink.
#F
#I'll leave the door unlocked. That's what you want to drink.
Tell me
I've compiled a mandarin
database views drawn from
Shield FBI and CIA intercepts
initiating virtual crime
scene reconstruction.
#F
#Tell me I've compiled a mandarin database views drawn from Shield FBI and CIA intercepts initiating virtual crime scene reconstruction.
Okay, what do we got here?
#F
#Okay, what do we got here?
Name is an ancient Chinese
War mental meaning advisor to
the King South American
Insurgency tactics toxic a
Baptist preacher. It's
pageantry going on here lots
theater closed heat from the
blast was in excess of 3,000
degrees Celsius, and he
subjects within twelve point
five yards were vaporized
instantly. No bomb Parts
found in a three-mile radius
of the Chinese Theater Mosa.
#F
#Name is an ancient Chinese War mental meaning advisor to the King South American Insurgency tactics toxic a Baptist preacher. It's pageantry going on here lots theater closed heat from the blast was in excess of 3,000 degrees Celsius and he subjects within twelve point five yards were vaporized instantly. No bomb Parts found in a three-mile radius of the Chinese Theater Mosa.
time to be happy
#F
#time to be happy
What is the bomb not a bomb?
#F
#What is the bomb not a bomb?
any military victims not
according to public records
bring up the thermogenic
signatures again factoring 3,
000 degrees. The Oracle cloud
is completed analysis
accessing satellites and
plotting the last 12 months
of thermogenic occurrences
now,
#F
#Any military victims not according to public records bring up the thermogenic signatures again factoring 3,000 degrees. The Oracle cloud is completed analysis accessing satellites and plotting the last 12 months of thermogenic occurrences now,
Take away everywhere that
there's been a mandarin
attack.
#F
#Take away everywhere that there's been a mandarin attack.
Nope.
#F
#Nope.
that you sure that's not one
of his predates any known
Mandarin attack. The incident
was the use of a bomb to
assist a suicide.
#F
#That you sure that's not one of his predates any known Mandarin attack. The incident was the use of a bomb to assist a suicide.
The heat signature is
remarkably similar 3000
degrees Celsius.
#F
#The heat signature is remarkably similar 3000 degrees Celsius.
It's two military guys.
#F
#It's two military guys.
Ever been to Tennessee Jarvis
creating a flight plan for
Tennessee.
#F
#Ever been to Tennessee Jarvis creating a flight plan for Tennessee.