Mr Stark, hi there.
Our sources are telling us that all signs
are pointing to another Mandarin attack.
Anything else you can tell us?
Hey, Mr Stark.
When is somebody gonna kill this guy?
I'm just saying.
Is that what you want?
Here's a little holiday greeting
I've been wanting to send
to the Mandarin.
I just didn't know
how to phrase it until now.
My name is Tony Stark
and I'm not afraid of you.
I know you're a coward.
So I've decided
that you just died, pal.
I'm gonna come get the body.
There's no politics here.
It's just good old-fashioned revenge.
There's no Pentagon,
it's just you and me.
And on the off chance you're a man,
here's my home address.
10880 Malibu Point.
90265.
I'll leave the door unlocked.
That's what you wanted, right?
Bill me.
I've compiled
a Mandarin database for you, sir,
drawn from
S.H.I.E.L.D., FBI and CIA intercepts.
Initiating virtual crime scene
reconstruction.
Okay. What have we got here?
The name is an ancient Chinese war
mantle meaning "adviser to the king."
South American insurgency tactics.
Talks like a Baptist preacher.
There's lots of pageantry going on here.
Lots of theater. Close.
The heat from the blast was in excess
of 3,000 degrees Celsius.
Any subjects within 12.5 yards
were vaporised instantly.
No bomb parts found in a three-mile
radius of the Chinese Theater?
No, sir.
Talk to me, Happy.
When is a bomb not a bomb?
Any military victims?
Not according to public record, sir.
Bring up
the thermogenic signatures again.
Factor in 3,000 degrees.
The Oracle cloud
has completed analysis.
Accessing satellites
and plotting the last 12 months
of thermogenic occurrences now.
Take away everywhere
that there's been a Mandarin attack.
Nope.
That.
Are you sure that's not one of his?
It predates any known Mandarin attack.
The incident was the use of a bomb
to assist a suicide.
Bring her around.
The heat signature
is remarkably similar.
3,000 degree Celsius.
That's two military guys.
Ever been to Tennessee, Jarvis?
Creating a flight plan for Tennessee.