BROUGHT THEIR A GAME
TONIGHT, ONLY FIVE WILL SURVIVE.
IT'S "AMERICA'S GOT TALENT: THE
RESULTS!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
THREE WEEKS.
YES, JUST THREE WEEKS TILL I'M
UP HERE SAYING, "THE WINNER OF
AMERICA'S GOT TALENT 2020 IS" --
AND FILL IN THE NAME YOU WANT TO
HEAR
TONIGHT FIVE ACTS WILL MAKE IT
TO THE SEMIFINALS AND MOVE A
STEP CLOSER TO REACHING THAT
DREAM.
BUT FOR SIX, THIS WILL BE THE
END OF THE LINE.
THERE'S GOING TO BE JOY AND
HEARTBREAK IN THE NEXT HOUR, SO
STAY GLUED TO THAT CHAIR
THIS IS GONNA MOVE FAST!
LAST NIGHT, ONCE AGAIN, WE HAD
ALL KINDS OF ACTS FROM RIGHT
ACROSS AMERICA AND AROUND THE
WORLD.
IT WAS UP AND DOWN
SOPHIA HIT THE BUZZER.
>> THIS IS THE LAST CHANCE FOR
THEM TO GET TO THE SEMIFINALS.
>> I AM GOING TO CLEAN MY BUZZER
JUST IN CASE
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> Sofia: I AM SORRY, I WAS
SANITIZING
>> Howie: I JUST CAN'T SIT
I GET EXCITED.
>> Terry: WE HAVE PERFORMANCES
FROM AROUND THE GLOBE.
THEY ARE ALL FIGHTING FOR ONE
THING.
A SPOT IN THE SEMIFINALS
>> Howie: BRING ON THE TALENT.
>> Heidi: THEY ARE SO FULL OF
ENERGY
IT'S EXPLOSIVE
IT'S LIKE A SODA THAT YOU SHAKE.
>> Howie: THE QUESTION I HAVE
ABOUT THIS PARTICULAR
PERFORMANCE -- WAS IT BETTER
DID YOU UP IT FROM THE LAST
TIME
>> Heidi: YES, IT IS
>> Sofia: YEAH, DON'T START.
YOU GUYS DID A BETTER JOB THAN
THE FIRST TIME NO MATTER WHAT
THIS GUY SAYS.
>> Howie: THEY WERE GREAT.
I THINK THEY HAVE TO UP IT
>> Heidi: THEY DID UP IT
>> Heidi: I THINK YOU ARE
AMAZING AND I LOVE THE BOND YOU
HAVE WITH YOUR SISTER.
♪♪
>> Howie: THAT SONG DIDN'T DO IT
FOR ME PERSONALLY.
♪ DANCE ME THROUGH THE STARS ♪
>> Howie: IS THAT A WELL-KNOWN
SONG
>> Heidi: SHE JUST SAID THAT SHE
WROTE IT FOR HER SISTER.
HOWIE IS OFF
>> Howie: IT'S SO SAD, I DON'T
LIKE IT.
>> Howie: I FOUND THAT
REFRESHING
I LOVED THE FIRST TIME YOU WERE
ON THE STAGE BUT I COULDN'T TELL
YOU WHAT THE MESSAGE IS.
>> Heidi: WE ARE ALL COOPED UP
IN OUR SPACES AND SAYING HEY, DO
SOMETHING FOR THE PERSON NEXT
DOOR LIVING ALONE.
>> Howie: IN THE FIRST TIME THE
DOG TOLD A STORY
>> Heidi: THEY DIDN'T HAVE TIME
TO MAKE NEW PUPPETS.
>> Howie: PEOPLE WILL STEP UP
AND DO IT DIFFERENTLY.
YOU GUYS KEEP BOOING ME.
>> Sofia: THERE IS HAND
SANITIZER HERE
>> WHEN YOU GET ON THE WORLD
STAGE LET THE PEOPLE KNOW WE ARE
THE DIVAS AND DRUMMERS OF
COMPTON!
♪♪
>> Heidi: I LOVED THE
CHOREOGRAPHY
YOU GUYS ARE INSPIRING
>> Howie: SO FAR THIS HAS BEEN
MY FAVORITE ACT OF THE NIGHT
DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU HAVE.
>> THIS IS A SURPRISE.
I HAVE FIVE MONTHS NOW
>> Howie: DIVAS AND DRUMMERS,
I'M IN A BETTER MOOD NOW
♪♪
>> Heidi: THREE BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE
WITH THREE BEAUTIFUL VOICES.
>> Howie: YOU GUYS SET A BAR AND
I THINK THAT BAR IS STILL SET.
AMERICA IS GOING TO HAVE TO
DECIDE
♪♪
>> Heidi: YES, YES, YES, YES
BEAUTIFUL!
♪♪
>> Heidi: HI CELINA.
>> IT MEANS A LOT THAT "AGT" HAS
LET ME BE MYSELF
>> Heidi: YOU NAILED IT.
>> Howie: YOU HAVE TO UP YOUR
GAME
AND THEY ARE GOING TO REMEMBER
YOU.
>> Sofia: YOU ARE THE HIGHLIGHT
OF THE NIGHT
BRAVO!
IF THIS WAS A GOLDEN BUZZER I
WOULD GIVE IT TO YOU
I CAN'T.
HOWIE, GET A PICTURE FOR THE
SOCIAL MEDIA
>> Heidi: TRY A LITTLE HARDER.
>> Sofia: COME ON, HEIDI
>> Terry: NOAH EPPS!
>> Sofia: YOU HAVE A STRONG
SENSE OF YOU DO WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO
I THINK THAT'S AMAZING AT YOUR
AGE AND I THINK YOU ARE GOING TO
BE HUGE.
>> HOWIE, A 40-YEAR CAREER, THAT
TAKES DRIVE WHEN YOU LOOK LIKE A
TURTLE --
>> Sofia: THIS GUY IS DESTROYED
AND HE'S CLAPPING.
>> SOFIA, I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS
MORE SUPPORTIVE, YOUR FAMILY OR
YOUR BRA
>> Sofia: YOU ARE MEAN.
[ BUZZER ]
>> Heidi: ROSES ARE RED, VIOLETS
ARE BLUE, SOME PEOPLE ARE FUNNY,
NOT SURE ABOUT YOU
♪♪
>> Heidi: WHAT A GREAT
COMBINATION OF TALENT AND THREE
STUNNING WOMEN
>> Sofia: I DON'T SEE A REASON
WHY YOU GUYS WOULD NOT HAVE YOUR
DREAM OF BEING IN VEGAS.
>> Howie: TO THINK THAT ONE OF
THEM STILL HAS A DAMAGED KNEE
AND WERE STILL DOING THAT.
♪♪
>> Howie: I LIKE THE SONG.
>> Heidi: YOU HAD YOUR SECOND
CHANCE
I THINK YOU USED IT WELL
I AM SO EXCITED THAT YOU GUYS
ARE HERE
♪♪
>> Sofia: YOU REMIND ME OF ALL
AMERICAN GOOD MEN.
>> Howie: LIKE ME.
>> Sofia: NO, YOU ARE CANADIAN
>> HAVING A CHANCE TO COME BACK
HERE AS THE COMEBACK BOYS.
I'M THANKFUL FOR IT.
I LOVE YOU, DEAR
>> I DO, TOO
>> BE AMERICA'S NEXT MOST
POPULAR ASSET.
A COMPANY OF A VIDEO MY MOTHER'S
BIGGEST FEAR IS THAT I WON'T
RETURN HOME.
MY MOTHER WARNED ME, DON'T GET
CAUGHT AT THE WRONG PLACE AT THE
WRONG TIME WITH THE WRONG
COLORED SKIN WITH THOSE THREE
STRIKES THAT LEADS TO PINE BOX
I NEED YOU TO RETURN HOME.
>> Howie: MY GOD
>> Heidi: YOU SPOKE TRUE WORDS,
HONEST WORDS, NECESSARY WORDS.
THANK YOU.
>> Howie: THIS IS ABOVE AND
BEYOND ANYTHING I HAVE SEEN OR
ANYTHING I HAVE HEARD.
I AM SO PROUD TO BE IN THIS
ROOM
HAS YOUR MOTHER HEARD THAT
>> NO, FIRST TIME NOW.
>> Howie: YOU ARE MY FAVORITE.
>> DEDICATED TO MY MOTHER.
LOVE YOU
>> Heidi: CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I AGREE
WITH YOU TODAY
>> Sofia: I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS
IS MY JOB, TO SEE ALL THESE
PEOPLE, ALL OF THESE DREAMS COME
TRUE
>> Terry: AMERICA, LET'S HEAR IT
FOR YOUR QUARTER FINALISTS
LOOK AT THESE ACTS
BY THE END OF TONIGHT, FIVE OF
THEM WILL BE THROUGH TO THE
SEMIFINALS, BUT SIX WILL BE
HEADING HOME
YOU CAN CUT THE ATMOSPHERE WITH
A KNIFE UP HERE -- IT'S SO TENSE
RIGHT NOW.
WATCHING AND WAITING TO HEAR IF
THEIR FAVORITES ARE THROUGH.
WE HAVE PEOPLE SPREAD OUT ACROSS
THE NATION
AND RIGHT DOWN IN FRONT, WE HAVE
GOT THREE PEOPLE SPREAD OUT
ACROSS THE JUDGES' DESK.
MAKE SOME NOISE FOR HEIDI KLUM,
HOWIE MANDEL AND SOFIA VERGARA
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
>> LAST NIGHT WAS INSANE
WHAT IS YOUR TAKE ON IT?
>> Sofia: I'M NERVOUS BECAUSE I
HAVE A LOT OF HOPE FOR THIS
AMAZING GROUP OF PEOPLE.
I WISH THEY COULD ALL GO IN AND
BE PART OF THAT GROUP, BUT WE
HAVE TO SEE WHAT AMERICA DECIDED
LAST NIGHT
>> Terry: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
TO IT.
THE SEMIFINALS START NEXT WEEK
BASED ON YOUR VOTES FROM LAST
NIGHT, THREE ACTS WILL GO
STRAIGHT THROUGH
BUT THE ACTS WHICH CAME IN
FOURTH, FIFTH AND SIXTH ARE IN
DANGER OF GETTING SENT HOME --
UNLESS YOU THROW ONE OF THEM A
LIFELINE WITH TONIGHT'S LIVE
DUNKIN' SAVE VOTE.
IN NO PARTICULAR ORDER, HERE ARE
THE ACTS ON THE BUBBLE
BELLO SISTERS OVER IN GERMANY,
CELINA, AND RESOUND.
PLEASE STEP FORWARD.
SO WHICH ONE DO YOU WANT TO
SAVE
THE VOTE IS OPEN NOW
YES IT'S HAPPENING NOW, SO GET
BUSY
YOU'VE GOT 30 MINUTES TO VOTE
USING THE "AGT" APP, OR GO TO
NBC.COM.
IF YOU'RE IN ANOTHER TIME ZONE,
DOWNLOAD THE "AGT" APP OR FOLLOW
US ON TWITTER AND FACEBOOK AND
EACH WEEK WE'LL LET YOU KNOW
WHAT TIME THE DUNKIN' SAVE IS
OPEN, SO YOU CAN VOTE TOO.
HOWIE, DID YOU EXPECT TO SEE
THESE THREE ACTS UP HERE
>> Howie: NO, I'M ACTUALLY
SURPRISED.
RESOUND AND CELINA AND THE BELLO
SISTERS, YOU WERE PART OF THE
SHOW WHEN IT TURNED AROUND FOR
ME PERSONALLY.
I LOVED ALL THREE OF YOU
I THINK LAST NIGHT WAS PROBABLY
THE TOUGHEST NIGHT FOR AMERICA
AND THE TOUGHEST NIGHT FOR THE
DUNKIN' SAVE
YOU ALL DESERVE TO BE SAVED.
START VOTING, PEOPLE
>> Terry: WELL, YOU CAN ONLY
SAVE ONE OF THEM
WHICH IS IT GOING TO BE?
YOUR VOTES WILL DECIDE, SO GET
TO IT.
AND ALSO, COMING UP, SENSATIONAL
COUNTRY STAR CAM WILL BE HERE
WITH ONE OF OUR ALL-TIME
FAVORITE "AGT" ACTS,
DUO TRANSCEND, AND WE FINALLY
GET TO CHECK OUT SOFIA VERGARA'S
FAMOUS VENTRILOQUIST SKILLS.
ARE THEY AS GOOD AS SHE SAYS
WE'LL FIND OUT
AND STAY RIGHT HERE BECAUSE
"AGT" WILL BE BACK IN JUST ONE
MINUTE